Guide to the Committee on Canadian Studies, Yale University, Records of Robin Winks
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Committee on Canadian Studies, Yale University, records of Robin Winks
1967-1987
RU 358
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1.25
The records consist of files maintained by Robin Winks as a member of the Committee on Canadian Studies, a council of the Yale Center for International and Area Studies.
Yale Center for International and Area Studies
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 37 (YRG 37), Records of associations, institutes, centers, and organizations affiliated with Yale University.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of files maintained by Robin Winks as a member of the Committee on Canadian Studies, a council of the Yale Center for International and Area Studies.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged by accession.
Research institutes; Canada -- Study and teaching; Yale Center for International and Area Studies
- Records, circa 1976-1983; Accession 1998-A-055
  - Bicentennial Committee for International Conferences of Americanists, 1975-1980 (Box 1, Folder 1 - 2)
  - Canada and Yale, 1975-1978 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Canadian Chair, 1976-1981 (Box 1, Folder 10 - 11)
  - Canadian gifts (e.g., money and books), 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Canadian Studies at Yale, 1976-1981 (Box 1, Folder 14 - 18)
  - Canadian Studies: accounting, 1978-1981 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Canadians visit 5/21/75, 1975 May (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence
    - 1981 (Box 1, Folder 21 - 22)
    - 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 23 - 25)
    - Concerning donation to Canadian Studies, 1981-1984 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Re: brochure, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Financial statements for Canadian companies, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Joe Clark visit, 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Montreal alumni list, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Richard Dalon visit, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Study of Canada at Yale, R. Winks donation?, [ca. 1975] (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Yale graduates foreign services lists, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 38)